airportia.com 2019-12-24

# About Airportia. The Airport Guide.

## About Airportia

Airportia is a leading Flight Tracker, Airport & Airline information website.

Please note that Aiportia does not offer any way to contact Airports or Airlines. If you would like to contact an Airport or an Airline please visit their respective websites and use their contact forms or email addresses in order to contact them directly. If you send a message intended for an Airport or an Airline to the email below, your message will not reach the intended recipient and you will not get an answer.

If you would like to contact the website Airportia.com please email us at [airportia.com@gmail.com](mailto:airportia.com@gmail.com)

## Privacy Policy

Airportia.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.airportia.com

**Information Automatically Logged**

We only use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. We do not use cookies in any other parts of our Web site; cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**Personal Information**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you. We only collect email addresses of those visitors of the site that send us their feedback. We personally contact those visitors and answer their personal questions.

We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Airportia.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
